< JULIA NOIRET />

Full Stack Web Developer

WHO I AM

I am a passionate web developer with a creative mindset who has just completed Le Wagon web development bootcamp, ranked by students best bootcamp in the world. From my background in hospitality, sales and customer relationship, I developed a customer focused mindset, essential to design websites tailored for my clients and users. I have always had an interest in design and I am particularly conscious of the user interface and experience.

PORTFOLIO



LINKEDIN PROFILE



GITHUB PROFILE



JULIA.NOIRET@GMAIL.COM



0423 286 151



PROJECTS

- Designed, implemented and shipped to production a Rails prototype of a web application in a team of 4 people in 2 weeks: <u>Mountain Maps</u>
- Designed, implemented and shipped to production a clone of Airbnb in team of 4 people in 5 days
- Designed 2 responsive website templates using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap & JavaScript (before bootcamp)

WORK EXPERIENCE

- 2017-2020 (2 years & 8 months): various experiences in hospitality as
 Bartender & Waitress (QLD & TAS, Australia)
- 2015-2016 (10 months): various experiences working on farms (quality controller, administration officer, grading, packing) (NT & QLD, Australia)
- 2013-2014 (1 year): **Relationship Manager**, Vivamural, Lille (France)
- 2012-2013 (9 months): **Store Supervisor**, Yves Rocher, Flers (France)
- 2011-2012 (1 year & 4 months): **Sales Team Leader**, Yves Rocher, Douai (France)

EDUCATION

- Web development coding bootcamp 10 weeks Le Wagon Melbourne (Australia) - 2021
- Certificate Interactivity with JavaScript and Advanced Styling with Responsive Design - HTML5 and CSS3 - Coursera (online courses) - University of Michigan - 2019/2020
- Bachelor of Business Administration IAE Lille (France) 2014

SKILLS

FULL STACK SKILLS

- Learned the core concepts of programming and practiced it on Ruby, Rails and ES6
- Designed a database and built queries with SQL
- Optimized and responsive UI/UX with Flexbox, CSS grid and Bootstrap
- Worked in team & on pair programming and by using version control tools

SOFT SKILLS

Creativity | Work Ethic | Collaborative | Adaptability | Empathy | Desire to learn

